HELEN GUNBY

| BIRMINGHAM B25 8EA | +44 (0)7806 790539 |

| gunby.helen@gmail.com | LinkedIn http://linkedin.com/in/helen-gunby/ | GitHub http://github.com/tnarus |
Nationality: British | IASSC SSGB, ITIL

Energetic, motivated, effective analyst with over 10 years of professional experience in data management and quality roles for demanding employers in a wide range of sectors including Cloud SaaS IT, automotive engineering and fin-tech. Current participant in Tech Talent Academy's Data Academy programme learning Python fundamentals, including key data science libraries such as Numpy, Pandas, SciKit, and TensorFlow. Additionally, I am gaining a solid grounding in machine learning algorithms, relational database management (SQL, Workbench), data visualisation/business intelligence packages such as PowerBI, and R programming language. My current career objective is to make a contribution in a challenging data science role in the leading environment that encourages excellent presentation, recognition, and development where I could empower colleagues and promote integrity with the help of my resourceful work experience and personal skills.

KEY SKILLS

Data Management, Analysis, Python Predictive Dashboards & Tableau Case Resolution, Planning & Delivery Salesforce Trailhead Ranger, earned 10 superbadges Lightning Process Builder & Flows Practical Problem Solving & New Process Design

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HALFORDS, REDDITCH, UK

OCT 2021 - present

UK's leading automotive and cycling retailer with more than 700 stores and over 10,000 colleagues. Salesforce Administrator | Support

As the Salesforce Administrator of Halfords, I will be responsible for Support department Service Cloud process improvement, Salesforce Commerce platform B2C usability as well as the implementation of machine learning algorithms in predictive AI Salesforce Chat Bot for the customers of Halfords.

ADVANCED, BIRMINGHAM, UK

FEB 2016 - OCT 2021

Third-largest, fastest growing UK-based software provider with revenues of £200 million and over 2,000 staff. Application Administrator | BOSS

Partnering with key functions to implement innovation within Salesforce and the wider Business Operating System Standards (BOSS) solutions. Managing Service Cloud & Sales Cloud apps and Experience Cloud (formerly Community Cloud) used by 1000+ of customers both internally and externally as an administrator of Salesforce. Data governance, role development and permissions control.

Technical support lead for migrating Docman and Careworks 100+ users from existing CRMs to Salesforce Lightning and for Support function migration from Classic to Lightning Experience. Product and SKU builds completion in CPQ.

Coordinated with the external development team (Make Positive, Inc) in resolving challenging problems, implementing agreed remedies, new processes and preventative measures. Provisioned and maintained technical knowledge base and manuals, helping to improve efficiency of training of new starters and promote effective Salesforce usability among teams. Prince's Trust Million Movers 2020 team member for marketing and engagement.

Support Consultant | Support

Delivered dedicated IT Support (1st and 2nd line) and highly valued customer service by resolving logged incidents, service requests and escalations in line with the service level agreements (SLAs) for bespoke educational MIS (management information system) cloud and SQL products used by University College London, University of Oxford, The BRIT School and other leading establishments.

Co-supported the UK's biggest Academy Trusts smooth transition to CloudSchool, a leading MIS in the Advanced product portfolio, a SaaS-based second generation MIS with a comprehensive suite of analytical SSRS (SQL Server Reporting Services) reports.

Acquired Information Security, Product Systems, Business Functions and ITIL® training. Net Promoter Score (NPS) Champion, engaged and supported the team to promote NPS and reached the highest support team scores in 2018 and 2019.

JAGUAR LAND ROVER, EMC, WEST MIDLANDS, UK JAN 2015 – JAN 2016

UK's largest car manufacturer with £25.8 billion yearly revenue.

Quality Assurance Systems Coordinator

Promoted within six weeks of employment as a quality coordinator for supplier parts; progressed to role that exploited strong technology skills. Created best practice quality administration function, including QA reports, job authorisation documentation, audit processes and ensuring stringent accuracy of WES/QPS processes; collaborated closely with onsite contractor colleagues and JLR stakeholders.

Delivered faultless reporting and management of key schedules, including payroll, staffing, attendance and daily activity reports record, as well as submission of rigorously accurate daily final EXEC report on quality operations. Provided continuous improvement across routine administrative processes; enhanced efficiency against KPIs with JLR POWERTRAIN, FMEA, DMAIC and Root Cause Analysis principles. Devised and delivered training for >30 new colleagues; instrumental to successful induction processes.

UBS, LONDON, UK

FEB 2013 - SEP 2014

Co-headquartered in the cities of Zürich and Basel, it is the largest Swiss banking institution in the world. Private Banking Executive Assistant

Assisted in managing a portfolio of equity based investments for UK, Swiss and select Russian domiciles. Successfully worked with a diverse range of high profile customers with various cultural backgrounds, mind sets and expectations. Provided location-based consultations across Europe.

EDUCATION

Masters in Branding and Identity, University of the Arts, London, 2014-2016.

Awarded Distinction in Information Design, a module focused on presentation of visually optimised data.

Delivered statistical analysis of large amounts of data; collaborated with Ph.D. Researcher Ben Wilson, Department of Social Policy, LSE. Mapped movement, settlement and employment of migrants coming from 'Accession A8 Countries'.

Published: ©P Hilton, S Tsirogianni, M W Bauer, LSE 2014.

BSc in Computer Science, University of Latvia, 2009.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION

BCS Foundation Award in Machine Learning, TTA, 2021

Level 2 Certificate in Business Administration, Herefordshire & Ludlow College, 2019

Level 2 Certificate in Equality & Diversion, Herefordshire & Ludlow College, 2018

ITIL® Foundation Cert in IT Service Management, Nov 2018.

Lean Six Sigma Green Belt, IASSC, Feb 2016.

Lean Management, Project Management Institute, July 2015.

PERSONAL

Keen mountaineer, climbed peaks of Mont Blanc in French Alps (2011) and Mount Elbrus in the northern Caucasus Mountains (2009).

Volunteer, Amnesty International Ukraine Crisis Initiative, 2014 – present.

Fin-Techie, curious about Artificial Intelligence latest developments, Sci-fi movies, cryptocurrencies and block chain technology; attends scientific exhibitions and festivals – STARMUS 2017-2019.

IT Skills: MS Office, advanced Excel incl. pivot tables and Visual Basic, MS Project, Adobe CC, Tableau, SSRS, SQL, WordPress, XML, Salesforce, Salesforce Dataloader, Workbench, CPQ.

Workshops: Business Innovation with Strategy & Leadership and Envisioning for Growth through Innovation at Aston University, Birmingham.